var myQuestions = [
    {
        question: "How many Hiroshima bombs would be equivalent in energy to the burritos Chipotle sold in 2015?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many universes can fit inside an average cat?",
        answer: -83
    },
    {
        question: "How many words are there in a standard Merriam-Webster Dictionary?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many meters is it from New York to Los Angeles?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "If the company is able to create 10 sheets of paper per second, how many hours would it take to convert General Sherman into paper?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many prime numbers are there less than 1 septillion?",
        answer: 22
    },
    {
        question: "Call the electrostatic force of attraction between an electron and a proton separated by a distance of 1m A. Call the gravitational force of attraction between the same particles separated by the same distance B. Compute B/A.",
        answer: -40
    },
    {
        question: "Because you are a competitor of culture, you only compete in Inquiry & Nature of Science events. Let X be the set of letters contained in the combined names of all 2018 Inquiry & Nature of Science events. How many English words only contain letters in X?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many times will the average person’s heart beat in his/her life?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "Suppose a businessperson flew roundtrip between New York City and San Francisco once every week for 15 years. How many chest x-rays worth of radiation would this person have accumulated?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is (69 choose 42)?",
        answer: 19
    },
    {
        question: "What is the voltage of the average lightning bolt?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many light years are there in 30 kiloparsecs?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "If every person in the world exhaled at the same time and we collected all the exhaled carbon dioxide, how many yards would we need to drive a standard American pick-up truck in order to match this quantity of carbon dioxide through the burning of gasoline?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many cubic centimeters of diesel fuel are consumed by a cruise liner the size of Queen Elizabeth II on a voyage of 100 nautical miles?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How​ ​many​ ​king​ ​size​ ​beds​ ​would​ ​it​ ​take​ ​to​ ​​blanket​ ​​the​ ​surface​ ​of​ ​the​ ​Pacific​ ​Ocean?",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "How many spines does a small cactus have?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Due to the height disparity, Antonio crushes Chris with the final score being 100^2018 to 0. During the game, Antonio scored either two-pointers or three-pointers. How many possible combinations of two and three pointers (disregarding ordering) could Antonio have made?",
        answer: 4035
    },
    {
        question: "How long of a line could you draw with a standard pencil, in mm?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "What percentage of Earth’s total mass is made up of humanity?",
        answer: -11
    },
    {
        question: "How long does it take to fly around the world in hours?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the average distance in millimeters between the particles of an ideal gas at STP?",
        answer: -6
    },
    {
        question: "What is the population of left-handed women in Japan?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "What is the amount of bean production in the united states in short tons per year?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many basketball shots are attempted each year in America?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many pizzas are sold in the US each year?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many nanometers are in a megaparsec?",
        answer: 31
    },
    {
        question: "How many planet earths could you line up along the equator of the sun?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many atoms thick is a piece of 65lb weight paper [#]?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "What is the least number of General Shermans needed to reach the moon from Earth?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many centimeters of blood vessels are in the average adult human?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "How much land in square meters would be needed to supply US Electrical needs in solar energy?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "The number of live births in Haiti minus the number of deaths",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many Americans are affected by Hemophilia?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "If Peter Salovey decided to use Yale's endowment to buy real estate at the same price that Jefferson bought the Louisiana Purchase (without inflation), how much land could Peter Salovey buy, in Earths?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many gallons of gasoline were consumed by cars in the U.S. in 2003?",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "Consider the combustion of propane (C3H8). How many moles of propane would you need to combust in order to release the same amount of energy that the Sun outputs in an hour? Assume that oxygen (O2) is in excess and that ∆H = −2221 kJ/mol.",
        answer: 24
    },
    {
        question: "How many Olympic-sized swimming pool can the Atlantic Ocean fill?",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "Consider all the water molecules from the previous question. If they were all placed side by side, what percentage of the distance from New York City to Chicago would that cover? [Previous question: How many water molecules are in a single drop of pure water?]",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How long would it take an ostrich to run the distance from Seattle to San Diego, in hours?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the diameter of the sun divided by the diameter of a human red blood cell?",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "How many liters of water flows out of the Amazon River each year?",
        answer: 16
    },
    {
        question: "Bill Gates could fully fund how many construction projects to renovate Speedway Mall at UT?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How fast (in miles per hour) would a satellite be traveling if it were 100 miles above the surface of the earth and completed one orbit every 90 minutes?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How massive is a mole of cats in kilograms?",
        answer: 24
    },
    {
        question: "The lower limits of human hearing in MegaHertz",
        answer: -5
    },
    {
        question: "How many peanuts does a 16 oz. jar of natural creamy peanut butter contain?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How hot could the Sun’s energy outputted in a second heat up the Atlantic Ocean? Assume all of the Sun’s heat energy goes directly to warming up the ocean.",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many pennies, lying flat, would it take to cover the area of Kansas?",
        answer: 15
    },
    {
        question: "If you jumped on a planet with the mass of the Sun, how high above the ground could you jump in millimeters?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many quills does an average porcupine have?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "The Kilocalories burned by 150 sedentary 150 lb females in 150 days",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "Per capita income in the Pittsburgh",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many eggs are consumed in the city of Stockton each year?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many pennies would you need to stack to reach the height of Mount Everest?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "Estimate 613!",
        answer: 1444
    },
    {
        question: "If we placed Nissan Quest minivans (2001 model) from head to tail, how many would we need to wrap around the equator?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many turkeys were consumed during November and December in 2012 in the United States?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many people in the world are left-handed?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many toothpicks does it take to travel across the observable universe?",
        answer: 28
    },
    {
        question: "What is the distance of the ground state electron in Hydrogen to the nucleus in picometers?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "If a major earthquake occurred in San Francisco, California, how many milliseconds would pass before the resulting shear wave reached Syracuse, New York?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many golf balls would it take to fill an olympic sized swimming pool?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many Americans travelled for Thanksgiving in 2017, according to AAA?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many likes does the most-viewed Youtube video in 2009, The Evolution of Dance, currently have?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many cans of Dr. Pepper would it take to completely fill the International Space Station with Dr. Pepper?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "You go back to campus and its time for the award ceremony! You see Kresge Auditorium and, amazed at the engineering, you are reminded of MIT’s mascot, the beaver. How many aspen trees could a beaver gnaw down in the gestation period of a beaver, assuming it never stops and always works at peak performance?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many shoelaces would it take to span the length of the Suez canal?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many atoms are in the human body?",
        answer: 28
    },
    {
        question: "How many comments are written on Facebook on any given day?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many rolls of “Duck Brand 394468 All-Purpose Duct Tape” would it take to completely cover the surface of all the planets in our solar system? (hint: Pluto is not a planet).",
        answer: 17
    },
    {
        question: "Estimate the number of Oxygen molecules in the room. [Hints: Air is typically 21% oxygen. One mole of an ideal gas @ S.T.P. occupies 22.4 Liters of volume]",
        answer: 27
    },
    {
        question: "If you wanted to create a full-scale model of the orbits of all 8 planets in the solar system using paper clips, how many paper clips would you need?",
        answer: 15
    },
    {
        question: "How many attoseconds does it take for light to travel from the Earth to the moon and back?",
        answer: 18
    },
    {
        question: "21^(4!)",
        answer: 32
    },
    {
        question: "What is the current best estimate of the total number of fish in the ocean?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "How many prime numbers are there between 1 and the number 1 quadrillion?",
        answer: 13
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many times would you have to roll a standard six-sided die to have it show a six, ten times in a row?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "How many licks does it take to get to the center of a lolly pop?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many Escherichia coli bacteria, arranged end to end, would you need to reach across upstate New York?",
        answer: 15
    },
    {
        question: "How many standard 2x2 Lego bricks do I need to stack on top of each other to create a stack as tall as the Empire State Building?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is Princeton’s endowment [$]??",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "How many gallons of paint would it take to fully cover Switzerland in a coat of paint (assuming Switzerland is a flat country)?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "What is the length of an average red ant, as a multiple of the thickness of a cell membrane?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many high school students are there in the U.S.",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many possible combinations are there for a standard 3x3 Rubik’s cube?",
        answer: 19
    },
    {
        question: "Yo mamma so fat, she took all the Big Macs sold in the US last year and gobbled ’em right up! How many pounds of fat are in yo mamma now? Assume that yo mama ain’t burning any o’ those calories, cuz ain’t nobody got time for that!",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "Determine the length of the Nile river divided by the radius of a helium atom.",
        answer: 17
    },
    {
        question: "How many years would it take an empty cement mixer truck to travel from Stockholm to Moscow?",
        answer: -3
    },
    {
        question: "How​ ​many​ ​US​ ​quarters​ ​would​ ​it​ ​take​ ​to​ ​stack​ ​them​ ​from​ ​the​ ​Earth​ ​to​ ​the​ ​surface of​ ​the​ ​Sun?",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "How many microseconds ago was the programming language Python first released?",
        answer: 15
    },
    {
        question: "On Earth, how many millimeters long would the string on a simple pendulum have to be to have a period of one minute?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "A​ ​new​ ​material​ ​is​ ​discovered​ ​that​ ​can​ ​withstand​ ​9000N​ ​when​ ​evenly​ ​distributed​ ​over​ ​a 1mx1m​ ​area.​ ​How​ ​many​ ​evenly​ ​distributed​ ​pennies​ ​(made​ ​from​ ​zinc)​ ​would​ ​it​ ​take​ ​to exceed​ ​what​ ​the​ ​material​ ​can​ ​withstand?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many Taco Bell restaurants are there in the US?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the maximum value of the sine function?",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "How many pounds of snow is all the snow in problem 3? (Problem 3: If 6 inches of snow fall on Washington, DC, how many cubic feet of snow is that?)",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "Unfortunately, the awards ceremony has been going on, you haven’t placed and your last event, Write It Do It, is coming up. You really want that medal and at this point you’d even pay for it. How much Ethereum would it cost to purchase a 2016 Rio Summer Olympics gold medal?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mass of the Earth measured in kg?",
        answer: 25
    },
    {
        question: "How many times can the ball in a ballpoint pen spin 360 degrees before the pen runs out of ink?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "If the Sun’s volume were to increase by the volume of the Earth, what percent would its volume increase?",
        answer: -4
    },
    {
        question: "How many ping pong balls would it take to cover the “roof sails” on the Sydney Opera House?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "And they do indeed tie with all perfect scores! This is nontrivially perturbing,” Antonio says. “The chances of this occurring is higher than all four of us getting hit by lightning at this moment,” claims a not-so-impressed Allen. “You’re wrong,” says Franklin. What is the probability of all four officers are hit by lightning independently on a rainy day?",
        answer: -24
    },
    {
        question: "How many Google searches were there in 2017?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "How many phone calls are going on at any given point in time across the world? (phone calls)",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "If all the land in mainland America was divided equally among all its inhabitants, how many square inches would each person get?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "What is the diameter of Jupiter, as a multiple of the height of Mount Everest?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many gallons of water does it take to produce a dozen eggs?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Convinced that Franklin has forgotten about them, Allen and Antonio decide to head back to the States. When they return, they find that good ol’ faithful Frank Wu had been waiting for them all along. Due to Antonio’s outstanding athleticism in swimming and walking, Franklin awards him a life-sized pure gold statue of Franklin himself. How much is this statue worth in dollars?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "How many possible configurations of a 2x2 Rubik’s cube are there?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "What is the age of the Earth in seconds?",
        answer: 17
    },
    {
        question: "What is the number of playing cards that you would have to lay on the surface area of the Earth in order to fully cover it?",
        answer: 17
    },
    {
        question: "How many atoms are in a pound of sugar?",
        answer: 25
    },
    {
        question: "How many ping pong balls are needed to blanket the surface area of the Atlantic Ocean?",
        answer: 17
    },
    {
        question: "How many adult male African bush elephants equal the weight of the US national debt in pennies?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How much does Bill Gates’ net worth weigh in 10 dollar bills? Express your answer in grams.",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "In the entire history of the Academy Awards, how many movies have been nominated for Best Picture?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the distance from Pluto to the sun in kilometers?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "What is the total gravitational force on Earth, in newtons?",
        answer: 22
    },
    {
        question: "How many cells would fit in a gallon",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "What is the arc length of the earth in picometers ?",
        answer: -15
    },
    {
        question: "What is the total length of the Harry Potter movies measured in seconds?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "The number of sheets of paper used by students in an English class to write a 30 page term paper",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "About how many pounds of chocolate are sold the week leading up to Valentine’s Day in the US?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "How much carbon dioxide does the average American breathe out in his/her lifetime, in milliliters?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "What is the area, in square miles, of Alaska?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many sugar cubes would fit in the entire universe?",
        answer: 86
    },
    {
        question: "How many lumens per square foot does the Sun emit on Earth?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the diameter of a Helium atom divided by the diameter of the Sun?",
        answer: -16
    },
    {
        question: "What is the magnitude of the acceleration of the Earth due to the gravity of an apple near Earth’s surface? (m/s^2)",
        answer: -25
    },
    {
        question: "How many grains of sand exist on earth?",
        answer: 21
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mass of the ping pong balls that can fit in the volume of the amount of red blood cells produced by the human population in the amount of time the average person keeps their eyes closed in one lifetime?",
        answer: 15
    },
    {
        question: "What is the population of the world’s 70th most populous nation?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many hairs are on the average human head?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many ounces of turkey were consumed in the United States last year?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "What is the military budget of the United States, in US Dollars?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "How many Hot WheelsTMare sold in Austin every day?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How fast can a Maglev train go in mph?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is 137^56?",
        answer: 119
    },
    {
        question: "How many kilometers in width is the Amazon River during the wet season (at its widest)?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the growth rate of bamboo in furlongs per fortnight?",
        answer: -1
    },
    {
        question: "How many hair follicles are there on the world’s population? Assume humans only have hair follicles on their heads.",
        answer: 15
    },
    {
        question: "How many breaths does the average human take in a lifetime?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "Determine the distance from Pluto to the Sun divided by the diameter of Pluto.",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "Malcolm Brogdon has the highest free throw percentage in the NBA at 95.6% when this test was written. What is the probability that he misses two free throws in a row, assuming that each free throw is an independent event?",
        answer: -3
    },
    {
        question: "How​ ​many​ ​jumbo​ ​marshmallows​ ​does​ ​it​ ​take​ ​to​ ​equal​ ​the​ ​weight​ ​of​ ​General​ ​Sherman​ ​(a sequoia​ ​tree​ ​and​ ​the​ ​world's​ ​largest​ ​tree)?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many blades of grass are in a football field between end zones?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "How many gallons of water are produced by the heptane combustion of Problem 21? (Problem 21: How many gallons of gasoline were consumed by cars in the U.S. in 2003?)",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "How many electrons are there in a garbage can full of air sitting otherwise empty outside a student dormitory at Duke University.",
        answer: 26
    },
    {
        question: "How many times can light travel around the earth in one second?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many times does an average person blink in their lifetime?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "What is the gravitational attraction, in Newtons, between a 4-year-old kid and their Hot Wheels toy car when they’re at dinner and the car is in the toy box in the adjoining room?",
        answer: -12
    },
    {
        question: "How many cubic yards of concrete were used to build the Hoover Dam?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many Dalmatians are in the Walt Disney film about Dalmatians?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many moon does Saturn have?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many cans of soda could be produced from the fresh water frozen in the Earth's polar ice caps?",
        answer: 20
    },
    {
        question: "On average how many quarts of popped popcorn do Americans consume each year?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "What is the gravitational force (in newtons) between two adjacent pieces of paper in a closed book?",
        answer: -7
    },
    {
        question: "What is the area of Kansas in m^2?",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "How many M&Ms are needed to blanket the surface area of a queen-size mattress?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "At this very moment, throughout the skies around the world, how many people are in the air flying onboard an airplane?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "What is the height of the Great Pyramid of Giza, as a multiple of the height of the statue of liberty?",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "How many electrons are in a ‘normal-sized’ lightning bolt?",
        answer: 19
    },
    {
        question: "How many stars are visible from Earth, to the naked eye?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many Tesla Model S cars could you buy with the money used to build Carnegie Mellon’s David A. Tepper Quadrangle?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many Skittles would it take to fill the Earth?",
        answer: 23
    },
    {
        question: "What​ ​is​ ​the​ ​length​ ​of​ ​an​ ​average​ ​red​ ​ant,​ ​as​ ​a​ ​multiple​ ​of​ ​the​ ​length​ ​of​ ​the​ ​Nile​ ​river?",
        answer: -9
    },
    {
        question: "How many teaspoons of concrete are needed to fill the volume of the Hoover Dam?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "How many servings of New York-style cheesecake would be needed to balance the total number of calories collectively burned by all the runners of the New York City Marathon each year?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "What is the greatest number of baseballs you could fit on a Football field without stacking?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many joules of energy do humans use annually?",
        answer: 20
    },
    {
        question: "What is the value in dollars of all of the owner-occupied houses in Florida?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "What is the wavelength for red light in millimeters?",
        answer: -3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the number of US dimes it would take to make a full scale model of the Empire State Building?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "How many drops of water does it take to equal the weight of a grand piano?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "What percentage of the global Polish population lives in New Zealand?",
        answer: -3
    },
    {
        question: "How much depth in meters would a lake lose per year if it uniformly covered an area of 50 km^2 and supplied a local town with a population of 40,000 people? (ignore any additions from rain etc)",
        answer: -1
    },
    {
        question: "How many pizzas are sold in U.S. each year?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many ways are there to shuffle a deck of cards such that all 4 of the same number are next to each other? (all 4 aces are adjacent, all 4 twos are adjacent, all 4 Jacks are adjacent, etc.)",
        answer: 27
    },
    {
        question: "What is 1 atmospheric pressure in Pascals?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many humans have existed on Earth?",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "How many results are given when “Fermi Questions” is Googled?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many ping pong balls can fit into a Boeing 747?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "If the entire earth was covered with solar panels, how much energy would be produced in 1-year in kilowatt-hours?",
        answer: 18
    },
    {
        question: "How many cubic meters would the cargo hold of Santa’s sleigh have to be to carry a twelve-inch action figure for every girl and boy in the world?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How many students have graduated from Acton Boxborough Regional High School?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many total kilometers do all Americans drive in one year?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "How many new, unsharpened, standard-sized pencils laid end to end along the longest axis would it reach from the sun to the Galactic center of the Milky Way?",
        answer: 21
    },
    {
        question: "What is the total number of points scored by any NBA team in the 2017-2018 season? (points)",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "Archimedes famously placed an upper bound on the number of grains of sand needed to fill the entire universe: One vigintillion. How many grains of sand did he suggest?",
        answer: 63
    },
    {
        question: "How many pixels are uploaded to YouTube every day? Assume there is no compression and videos are 720p.",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "A satellite is placed in geosynchronous orbit around Earth. What is its speed in feet per second?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the number of board game dice it would take to fill a Hindenburg class airship?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "Compute 19^95.",
        answer: 121
    },
    {
        question: "What is the age of the earth in femtoseconds?",
        answer: 32
    },
    {
        question: "How much energy, in Joules, is released in a typical type II supernova from gravitational potential energy?",
        answer: 46
    },
    {
        question: "What is the kinetic energy in joules of a large truck at highway speed?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "If we covered the entire state of Kansas with a single layer of pennies, and then wanted to cover each penny with the maximum amount of water droplets without breaking surface tension, how many yoctoliters of water would we need?",
        answer: 36
    },
    {
        question: "How long is the smallest bee, Trigona minima, in meters?",
        answer: -3
    },
    {
        question: "Number of humans on planet Earth.",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "How many hot dogs are eaten at a Boston Red Sox game?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the estimated diameter of a carbon atom in centimeters?",
        answer: -8
    },
    {
        question: "How many hair follicles are on an average adult’s scalp?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mass in metric tons of a stack of US quarters as tall as the Washington Monument?",
        answer: -2
    },
    {
        question: "After building a human hovercraft, Wendy checks out the Mousetrap Vehicle (a vehicle powered by mousetraps). She sits in one of those rolly chairs and attaches a string to the vehicle and to the chair. When she releases the mousetrap, to her disappointment, the chair is not pulled forward. How many mousetrap does Wendy need to pull her across a room at 10 mph?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many hours would it take to count to 1 million?",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many seconds are there in a fortnight on Pluto?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "What is the temperature at the center of the Sun?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many miles of railroad track are in Ohio?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "The difference between the force of the moon on a particle at the Earth’s surface and between the force of the moon on a particle at the Earth’s center generates a tidal force. What is the ratio of the magnitude of the lunar tide force to that of the solar tide force?",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "The duration of all lightning strikes in the U.S. on any given day  in picoseconds",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "Every minute, how many red blood cells are produced in the average human body?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How long does it take a photon to travel the radius of a boron atom in a vacuum in seconds?",
        answer: -18
    },
    {
        question: "Given the same truck as described in the previous question, how many kilowatt-hours (kWh) would be generated if the volume of gasoline, required to transport this empty truck lengthwise across the state of Wyoming, were burned? (Previous question mentions a pick-up truck with a fuel efficiency of 200 millimiles per centigallon.)",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many dogs are there in the United States?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "How many meal worms would you need to stack on top of each other to reach the moon?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "How many gallons of gasoline were consumed by the U.S in 2017?",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "How many Volts does a standard potato battery produce?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the circumference of the earth in petameters?",
        answer: -8
    },
    {
        question: "How much would you make working for a year straight at California minimum wage.",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "What was the mass, in mg, of the turkeys from Problem #29? (Problem #29: How many turkeys were consumed during November and December in 2012 in the United States?)",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "How old is the oldest organism currently alive measured in atoms (the unit of time)?",
        answer: 12
    },
    {
        question: "Between 2009 – 2013, how many LED lights were installed to save energy in the U.S.?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many seconds is the average lifetime?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many words are there in the Second Edition Oxford English Dictionary?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "What is the half-life of Carbon-14?",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "Say you are standing in front of a sink and mirror ~ 1 meter away, how fast (in seconds) would you have to blink to see yourself completely blink in a bathroom mirror? (s)",
        answer: -9
    },
    {
        question: "What is the approximate density of the universe in kg/m^3?",
        answer: -28
    },
    {
        question: "On average, how many crayons does Crayola manufacture in a minute?",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "How many pennies are in $314,151,617,181,920.21?",
        answer: 16
    },
    {
        question: "How many hairs are on an adult black bear?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "If all of the candy corn alone that was sold at Halloween was laid out end to end, how many times would it circle the earth?",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What is the number of red blood cells in a drop of blood for an average human adult?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "How many turkeys are consumed at Thanksgiving each year?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "The mean volume of a single alveolus in a human lung. (μm^3)",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "Consider the combustion of butane (2C4H10 + 13O2 → 8CO2 + 10H2), which has an enthalpy of combustion of -2877.5 kJ/mol. How much energy, in Joules, would be released by reacting an Avogadro’s number of moles of butane with unlimited oxygen?",
        answer: 30
    },
    {
        question: "How many North Carolina’s can fit into Australia? (North Carolina)",
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How many cells are there in the human body?",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "If every human who has ever lived got together to push a giant rock over purely flat soil on Earth, what is the mass of the most massive rock, in kilograms, that they could push to overcome static friction with the ground (i.e. get it to move even just a teensy bit)?",
        answer: 13
    },
    {
        question: "How many inches thick is continental lithosphere?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "What is the average number of people playing fortnite on any given day?",
        answer: 6
    },
    {
        question: "How much water (in liters) is in the Atlantic Ocean and its adjacent seas?",
        answer: 20
    },
    {
        question: "The world’s largest ball of sisal twine in Cawker, KS has a mass of 20,324 pounds. If this twine was unrolled, how many times would it outline the perimeter of the state of Kansas?",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "What is the concentration in molarity of H+ in pure water?",
        answer: -7
    },
    {
        question: "How many teaspoonfuls of air would fit in the Oval Office?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "How many grams of caffeine would be found in Lake Erie if it were filled with Coca-Cola?",
        answer: 13
    },
    {
        question: "How many liters of water are there in Earth’s oceans?",
        answer: 21
    },
    {
        question: "What is the angular frequency of the fastest man-made spinning object in the world in rpm?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How long could the energy in a typical alkaline AA battery power a Bugatti Veyron for (in seconds)?",
        answer: -2
    },
    {
        question: "What is 30^30?",
        answer: 44
    },
    {
        question: "Highest 'Worldwide Box Office Gross' for a movie (US $)",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How much money, in USD, would you be spending on buying Minecraft in the previous question? (Previous question: How many Pixel 3s with the maximum storage capacity available for purchase would it take to download Minecraft Pocket Edition the same number of times as there are water molecules in a Dasani water bottle? (Assume that you can download multiple copies of a single game on each phone, and that 100% of the storage is going to storing Minecraft Mobile).)",
        answer: 26
    },
    {
        question: "How many teaspoons of air would fill the oval office?",
        answer: 8
    },
    {
        question: "How many grains of coarse sand can fill a Mason jar?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many server requests are made for 20M Internet users each hour?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "How many light years is it from Berwyn, PA to Chicago, Illinois?",
        answer: -10
    },
    {
        question: "How many giraffes are needed to fill a standard-sized shot glass?",
        answer: -2
    },
    {
        question: "What is the Earth’s equatorial circumference, measured in marathons?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the gravitational attractive force between the proton and electron in a hydrogen atom?",
        answer: -47
    },
    {
        question: "What mass of oxygen, in grams, will you consume through aerobic respiration during this Fermi Questions exam (presuming that you don’t die or hyperventilate so frantically as to skew the results)?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "The mass of a AAA battery would have to be condensed to a sphere of what radius before it becomes a black hole? Give your answer in meters.",
        answer: -29
    },
    {
        question: "The average American puts on 1.5 pounds during the winter holiday season. By how many Mg does the mass of the population of Kansas increase?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many photons are emitted from the sun per year (HINT: Assume that all of the photons have and energy of ≈ 10^(−19) J?",
        answer: 50
    },
    {
        question: "Since the time you were born, how far northward in millimeters has the continent of Australia drifted?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How many copies of this test will it take to fill the Pacific Ocean basin? Assume that this test is printed on standard letter-size paper.",
        answer: 15
    },
    {
        question: "How long in meters is the DNA in a single human cell?",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "How many bacterial cells in the body?",
        answer: 10
    },
    {
        question: "How many Lake Eries would it take to hold a pile of every credit and debit card in the world?",
        answer: -5
    },
    {
        question: "How many oxygen molecules enter your lungs on each inhalation?",
        answer: 23
    },
    {
        question: "How many km in 165 nm?",
        answer: -10
    },
    {
        question: "Number of states west of the Mississippi river?",
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How many grains of sand are there on Earth?",
        answer: 19
    },
    {
        question: "How old is the Earth, in seconds?",
        answer: 17
    },
    {
        question: "The airplane takes off! For some strange reason all twenty students are all taking different planes. What is the probability that all twenty planes are independently involved in a fatal crash?",
        answer: -138
    },
    {
        question: "What is 25! ?",
        answer: 25
    },
    {
        question: "What is the probability that I get a royal flush in a poker game?",
        answer: -3
    },
    {
        question: "A sverdrup is a unit of volumetric flow (m^3/s) roughly equiva- lent to the total rate of water flowing from rivers into oceans. The Antarctic Circumpolar current flows from Eastward (in the same direction as the Earth’s rotation), carrying water a rate of 150 sverdrups. If the current were to spontaneously stop, by how long would the length of day be shortened?",
        answer: -11
    },
    {
        question: "20^18",
        answer: 23
    },
    {
        question: "Velocity of the Earth moving around the Sun. (meters per second)",
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "A lightyear is equal to how many marathons?",
        answer: 11
    },
    {
        question: "What is the number of cells in a human body?",
        answer: 14
    },
    {
        question: "What is the half-life of Uranium-238 in years?",
        answer: 9
    },
    {
        question: "As a factor, how much more is the price of an Engineering degree from an average university than the price of an average new car?",
        answer: 0
    },
    {
        question: "How many milligrams of sugar are in a 1 L bottle of Coca Cola?",
        answer: 5
    },
    {
        question: "How many songs can fit on a 5GB flash drive?",
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mass of 1 atom of Nitrogen in kg?",
        answer: -26
    },
    {
        question: "How many electrons would you need to balance the weight of J.J. Thompson?",
        answer: 32
    },
    {
        question: "Annually, how many letters are lost in the mail in England?",
        answer: 7
    },
    {
        question: "What is the mass of an adult man divided by the mass of the Earth?",
        answer: -25
    },
    {
        question: "What is the average growth rate of a human fingernail in meters per second?",
        answer: -9
    },
    {
        question: "What is the weight in grams of the water in an Olympic sized swimming pool?",
        answer: 9
    }
]

// https://stackoverflow.com/questions/2450954/how-to-randomize-shuffle-a-javascript-array
function shuffle(array) {
    let currentIndex = array.length,  randomIndex;
  
    // While there remain elements to shuffle.
    while (currentIndex != 0) {
  
      // Pick a remaining element.
      randomIndex = Math.floor(Math.random() * currentIndex);
      currentIndex--;
  
      // And swap it with the current element.
      [array[currentIndex], array[randomIndex]] = [
        array[randomIndex], array[currentIndex]];
    }
  
    return array;
}

var questionNum = 0
var maxScore = 0
var score = 0

function getQuestion() {
    if (questionNum >= myQuestions.length) {
        document.getElementById("question").innerHTML = "<p> No more questions :( </p>"
    }
    else {
        document.getElementById("question").innerHTML = "<p>" + myQuestions[questionNum].question + "</p>"
    }
}

function getStanding() {
    document.getElementById("standing").innerHTML = `
    <p> You have ${score} points </p>
    <p> You are on question ${questionNum+1}/${myQuestions.length} </p>
    <p> Your current average is ${Math.round((score / questionNum) * 100) / 100} </p>`
}

function getResults() {
    var correctAns = myQuestions[questionNum].answer
    var ans = document.getElementById("answer").value
    if (correctAns == ans) {
        score += 5
        document.getElementById("results").innerHTML = "<p>Dead on! +5 points</p>"
    }
    else if (Math.abs(correctAns - ans) == 1) {
        score += 3
        document.getElementById("results").innerHTML = "<p>So close! You were 1 away, +3 points. The correct answer was " + correctAns + "</p>"
    }
    else if (Math.abs(correctAns - ans) == 2) {
        score += 1
        document.getElementById("results").innerHTML = "<p>Almost! You were 2 away, +1 point. The correct answer was " + correctAns + "</p>"
    }
    else {
        document.getElementById("results").innerHTML = "<p>Not quite! You were " + Math.abs(correctAns-ans) + " away, +0 points. The correct answer was " + correctAns + "</p>"
    }
    maxScore += 5
    questionNum += 1
    document.getElementById("answer").value = ""
}

function generateQuiz() {
    var input = document.getElementById("answer");
    input.addEventListener("keypress", function(event) {
    if (event.key === "Enter") {
        event.preventDefault();
        document.getElementById("submit").click();
    }
    });
    shuffle(myQuestions)
    getQuestion()
    getStanding()
    document.getElementById("submit").onclick = function(){
        getResults()
        getStanding()
        getQuestion()
    }
}

generateQuiz()